fatherprada.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Fatherprada

Welcome to our Privacy Policy  
— Your privacy is critically important to us.  
Fatherprada is located at:

Fatherprada  
5b Seye Ogunlewe street Igbogbo  
2347032803128

It is Fatherprada’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to fatherprada.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “fatherprada.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.  
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and Conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

– Website Visitors  
Like most website operators, Fatherprada collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Fatherprada’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Fatherprada’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Fatherprada may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
Fatherprada also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://fatherprada.com blog posts. Fatherprada only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

– Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information  
Certain visitors to Fatherprada’s websites choose to interact with Fatherprada in ways that require Fatherprada to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Fatherprada gathers depend on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://fatherprada.com to provide a username and email address.

– Security  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

– Advertisements  
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Fatherprada and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

-User Comments  
Certain parts of this website offer the opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions, information, material and data (‘Comments’) in areas of the website. Fatherprada does not screen, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their appearance on the website and Comments do not reflect the views or opinions of Fatherprada, its agents or affiliates. Comments reflect the view and opinion of the person who posts such view or opinion. To the extent permitted by applicable laws Fatherprada shall not be responsible or liable for the Comments or for any loss cost, liability, damages or expenses caused and or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.  
Fatherprada reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which it considers in its absolute discretion to be inappropriate, offensive or otherwise in breach of these Terms and Conditions.  
You warrant and represent that:  
You are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;

The Comments do not infringe any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark, or other proprietary rights of any third party;  
The Comments do not contain any defamatory, libellous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material or material which is an invasion of privacy  
The Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.  
You hereby grant to Fatherprada a non-exclusive royalty-free license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.  
Hyperlinking to our Content

– Links To External Sites  
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of every site you visit.  
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

-Iframes

Without prior approval and express written permission, you may not create frames around our Web pages or use other techniques that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Web site.

-Removal of links from our website

If you find any link on our Website or any linked web site objectionable for any reason, you may contact us about this. We will consider requests to remove links but will have no obligation to do so or to respond directly to you. Whilst we endeavour to ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we commit to ensuring that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.

-The following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:  
Government agencies;  
Search engines;  
News organizations;

Online directory distributors when they list us in the directory may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and  
Systemwide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.  
These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Web site information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.

We may consider and approve in our sole discretion other link requests from the following types of organizations: commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources such as Chambers of Commerce, American Automobile Association, AARP and Consumers Union;  
dot.com community sites; associations or other groups representing charities, including charity giving sites, online directory distributors; internet portals; accounting, law and consulting firms whose primary clients are businesses; and educational institutions and trade associations.

We will approve link requests from these organizations if we determine that: (a) the link would not reflect unfavourably on us or our accredited businesses (for example, trade associations or other organizations representing inherently suspect types of business, such as work-at-home opportunities, shall not be allowed to link); (b)the organization does not have an unsatisfactory record with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility associated with the hyperlink outweighs the absence of Fatherprada; and (d) where the link is in the context of general resource information or is otherwise consistent with editorial content in a newsletter or similar product furthering the mission of the organization.

These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Web site information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.

If you are among the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must notify us by sending an e-mail to mail@fatherprada.com Please include your name, your organization name, contact information (such as a phone number and/or e-mail address) as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Web site, and a list of the URL(s) on our site to which you would like to link. Allow 2-3 weeks for a response.

Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Web site as follows:

By use of our corporate name; or  
By use of the uniform resource locator (Web address) being linked to; or  
By use of any other description of our Website or material being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party’s site.  
No use of Fatherprada’s logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.

- Aggregated Statistics  
Fatherprada may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its website. Fatherprada may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Fatherprada does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

– Cookies  
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Fatherprada uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Fatherprada uses cookies to help Fatherprada identify and track visitors, their usage of https://fatherprada.com, and their website access preferences. Fatherprada visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Fatherprada’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Fatherprada’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.  
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Fatherprada’s use of cookies.

– E-commerce  
Those who engage in transactions with Fatherprada – by purchasing Fatherprada’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Fatherprada collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Fatherprada. Fatherprada does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Privacy Policy Changes  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Fatherprada may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Fatherprada’s sole discretion. Fatherprada encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept [Read More](https://fatherprada.com/)
